<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

	<g:ScrollPanel ui:field="scrollPanel">
		<g:HTMLPanel>
			<h1 style="font-face:Arial;">Introduction</h1>
			<p>Dear reader,</p>
			<p>Although the UIBinder chapter uses the S-Mart Login Form as the
				example widget throughout the chapter, there were several versions
				of
				this widget as well as several other examples that had nothing to
				do
				with the widget. To help you better understand the material we
				have
				created this demo, which includes in addition to the final
				LoginFormBox each version of the login form as well as the other
				examples.</p>
			<p>We hope that you learn as much from this Demo application as you
				do
				from each of the examples.</p>
			<p>
				<b>Show/Hide S-Mart Login</b>
				- This will display or hide the finished S-Mart login form as it
				was
				designed to be displayed, which is approximately the center of the
				page and overlaying any existing content.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>Show/Hide S-Mart Alt Login</b>
				- This will display or hide an alternately styled version of the
				login form. This was the original design but it had to be changed
				because it was too dark for use in the book. So we included it as an
				example of how to use the @UiTemplate annotation to provide two
				layouts for the same widget.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>S-Mark Login (v1)</b>
				- This will display version 1 of the login form, which has no
				styling
				and no event handling.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>S-Mark Login (v2)</b>
				- This will display version 2 of the login form, which included the
				additional error message HTML code in the template. Although the
				template fields are bound to the Java class, there is still no
				styling or event handling.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>DisclosurePanel Example</b>
				- An example of using the DisclosurePanel in the template with the
				header tag.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>SplitLayoutPanel Example</b>
				- An example of using the SplitLayoutPanel in the template with
				directional tags.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>Radio Buttons Example</b>
				- An example of using RadioButton in a template. RadioButton uses
				@UiConstructor to read the name attribute into the RadioButton
				constructor.
			</p>
			<p>
				<b>ClientBundle Example</b>
				- An example of using @UiFactory to create use a static instance of
				a ClientBundle and to ensure that a CssResource is properly
				initialized.
			</p>
		</g:HTMLPanel>
	</g:ScrollPanel>

</ui:UiBinder> 